<?xml version="1.0" ?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="songbook.css"?><songbook>

<song><songtitle>Amazing Grace</songtitle><artist>Traditional</artist><lyrics>
  C      C7        F        C
Amazing grace How sweet the sound
     C                   G     G7
That saved a wretch like me!
  C        C7        F     C
I once was lost, but now am found;
    C          G     C F C
Was blind, but now I see.
 
      C          C7        F        C
'Twas grace that taught my heart to fear,
    C              G       G7
And grace my fears relieved;
    C        C7       F      C
How precious did that grace appear
    C      G       C   F C
The hour I first believed.
 
        C    C7       F         C
Through many dangers, toils and snares,
  C           G      G7
I have already come;
     C          C7         F         C
'Tis grace hath brought me safe thus far,
    C          G       C  F   C
And grace will lead me home.
 
     D          D7        G        D
When we've been there ten thousand years,
       D              A    A7
Bright shining as the sun,
      D       D7      G          D
We've no less days to sing God's praise
     D         A       D    G D
Than when we'd first begun.

</lyrics></song>

<song><songtitle>Waltzing Mathilda</songtitle><artist>Banjo Paterson</artist><lyrics>
 D     A     D     A
 
D            A       D           G
Once a jolly swagman camped by a billabong
D                             A
Under the shade of a coolabah tree
D           A             D                   G
And he sang as he watched and waited till his billy boiled,
   D                   A            D
You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me 

			D                 G
			Waltzing Matilda, waltzing Matilda,
			   D        Bm         Em      A
			You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me.
				   D          A           D               G
			And he sang as he watched and waited till his billy boiled,
			   D                   A            D     A    D   A   D
			You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me.
 
D         A            D            G
Down came a jumbuck to drink at the billabong,
D                                          A
Up jumped the swagman and grabbed him with glee.
D           A            D                   G
And he sang as he shoved that jumbuck in his tucker bag,
   D                   A            D
You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me.
 
			CHORUS
 
D           A         D              G
Up rode the squatter, mounted on his thoroughbred,
D                             A
Up rode the troopers, one-two-three.
    D         A              D                  G
&quot;Where`s that jolly jumbuck, you`ve got in your tucker bag
  D                    A            D
You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me. 
 
			CHORUS
  
D             A            D              G
Up jumped the swagman and sprang into the billabong,
D                                 A
You`ll never catch me alive, said he
    D                A            D            G
And his ghost may be heard as you pass by that billabong,
   D                   A            D
You`ll come a-waltzing Matilda with me   
 
			CHORUS x 2
</lyrics></song>

<song>
<songtitle>Drunken Sailor</songtitle><artist>Traditional</artist><lyrics>
Em
What shall we do with the drunken sailor?
D
What shall we do with the drunken sailor?
Em
What shall we do with the drunken sailor?
Em    D       Em      
Ear-ly in the morning

		  Em
          Way, hey, an' up she rises,
          D
          Way, hey, an' up she rises,
          Em
          Way, hey, an' up she rises,
          Em   D         Em
          Ear-lye in the morning.

2)  Put him in the longboat 'till he's sober...

3)  Keep him there and make him bail 'er...

4)  Give him a dose of salt and water...

5)  Shave his belly with a rusty razor...

6)  Put him in bed with the captain's daughter...

7)  What shall we do with a drunken sailor?...
</lyrics></song>

<song>
<songtitle>This Year's Our Year</songtitle>
<artist>Jofish</artist>
<lyrics>
(Caz, 2021)
CHORUS: 
			C                                      C         
			Crack goes the bat! oooo goes the crowd 
			Am                                                                                         
			We cry so loud, it's the sound of the city,
															  Em
			&amp; the team, &amp; the town, &amp; the howl, &amp; the foul ball.
			F
			We've got a chance this year, 
			Got a chance this year,
			Got a chance this year
												G
			This year's.... our year
VERSE 1
C
We're here again, been away so long, so long old friend, since you've been gone
Am
Not the same without you,  seven dollar beers, two hot dogs, now alone with my feels
C
Pennants flying, lying to ourselves, we got this need this own this want this
Am
First in the league, first in the season, first of the teams, first is the reason
CHORUS (first line on F and G)
C
You don't call no more, can't call no more, no Paul no more, don't breath no more
Am
Down in the 7th, down in the league, down in the town, he needs to breath
C
O2 sats and earned run stats, moneyball, funnyball, ain't funny no more
Am
At the core it's a flaw and a chore and he claws back, back from the brink from the edge of it all
CHORUS
BRIDGE
Em                                           Am 
Last time he called was the start of May,    Mad about the roster, mad about the way
Em                                           Am 
Said he'd been feeling a little lightheaded, Didn't like the way that the team was headed
Em                                           Am 
Coughed a lot, complained a lot,             Said there was nothing to be sad or mad or do.
[heartbeat rhythm on E]
VERSE 3
Am
Airways can't clean, beeps the machine, worst I've seen, refused the vaccine 
C
Homerun at last, running for home, bases are loaded, everyone's home
Am 
First base second base, pitcher has thrown, hum of the ventilator, quiet groan
C
The bases are loaded, but nobody's home, FaceTime goodbyes, nurse holds the phone.
CHORUS (first line on F and G, end on C)
</lyrics></song>


  </songbook>